gradelink.com 2015-04-07

# Privacy Policy | Gradelink

##  Gradelink Privacy Policy

Last Updated on September 4th, 2008. 

* * *

We recognize that your privacy is important. This privacy policy applies to your use of Gradelink's website and anything related to the Service(collectively, the "Site"). We hope that by taking a few minutes to read our Privacy Policy, you will have a better understanding of what we do with the information you provide us and how we keep it both private and secure. 

The terms "we", "us", and "Gradelink" refer to the Gradelink Corporation. The terms "you" and "your" refer to you, as a user of the Site. The term "personal information" means information that you provide us which personally identifies you, such as your name, phone number, email address, and any other data that is tied to such information. 

BY USING THE SITE, YOU AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THESE TERMS, YOU SHOULD NOT USE THE SITE. 

* * *

#### 1\. Information We Collect and How We Use It

We use commercially reasonable efforts to ensure that the collection of personal information is limited to that which is necessary to fulfill the purposes identified below. If we use your information in a manner different than the purpose for which it is collected, then we will ask you for your consent prior to such use. 

**Account information.** If you create an account to take advantage of the full range of services offered on the Site, we ask for and record personal information such as your name and email address. We use your email address to send you updates and news, and contact you on behalf of your educational insitution. 

**Feedback.** If you contact us to provide feedback, register a complaint, or ask a question, we will record any personal information and other content that you provide in your communication so that we can effectively respond to your communication. 

**Activity.** We record information relating to your use of the Site, such as the pages you view, your browser type, IP address, requested URL, referring URL, and timestamp information. We use this type of information to administer the Site and provide the highest possible level of service to you. We also use this information in the aggregate to perform statistical analyses of user behavior and characteristics in order to measure interest in and use of the various areas of the Site. Web logs may also be used if necessary to help identify any person attempting to break into or damage our website, or use our websites to commit any illegal act. 

**Cookies.** We send cookies to your computer in order to uniquely indentify your browser and improve the quality of our service. The term "cookies" refers to small pieces of information that a website sends to your computer's hard drive while you are viewing the site. We may use both session cookies (which expire once you close your browser) and persistent cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them). Persistent cookies can be removed by following your browser help file directions. If you choose to disable cookies, some areas of the Site may not work properly. 

**Enforcement.** If we believe that we have evidence of a violation of computer security or related laws, we may use the information we collect in connection with your use of the Site (including your personal information and web logs) in order to investigate, enforce, and apply our Terms of Service and Privacy Policy. 

* * *

#### 2\. Transfer of Information

We may disclose your personal information to third parties in a good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to (a) take action regarding suspected illegal activities; (b) enforce or apply our Terms of Service and Privacy Policy; (c) comply with legal process, such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order; or (d) protect our rights, reputation, property, or that of our users, affiliates, or the public. Please note that we are not required to question or contest the validity of any search warrant, subpoena or other similar governmental request that we receive. 

* * *

#### 3\. Controlling Your Personal Data

As a registered Gradelink user, you can modify some of your personal information and your privacy preferences by accessing the "Account" section of this website. For example, you may choose not to receive e-mail alerts from Gradelink by accessing the "Alerts" tab on the Site and updating your notification settings. 

Gradelink will not share, trade or sell personal information of our visitors or customers for use by any business without your consent. Gradelink will share the information necessary to deliver products and services that you specifically request to receive but we will limit this information to only what is necessary and required to complete a transaction. 

* * *

#### 4\. Security

Your account is password protected. We use industry standard measures to protect the personal information that is stored in our database. We limit the access to your personal information to those employees who need access to perform their job function, such as our customer service personnel. If you have any questions about the security on the Site, please contact us. Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that your personal information will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy. 

You hereby acknowledge that Gradelink is not responsible for any intercepted information sent via the internet, and you hereby release us from any and all claims arising out of or related to the use of intercepted information in any unauthorized manner. 

Gradelink Corporation respects all applicable national and international children's privacy regulations. Gradelink does not intend to collect personal information from children. Gradelink complies with the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA) (20 USC §1232g, 34 CFR Part 99) which is a federal U.S. law that protects the privacy of student educational records. 

* * *

#### 4\. Links to other Sites

In the event that our website contains links to other websites, Gradelink, Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. We recommend you carefully read the privacy policies of each site you visit 

* * *

#### 5\. Terms and Modifications to this Privacy Policy

We may modify this Privacy Policy at any time, and we will post any new versions on this page. If we make any material changes in the way we use your personal information, we will notify you by sending an e-mail to the last e-mail address you provided to us and/or by prominently posting notice of the changes on our website. Any such changes will be effective upon the earlier of thirty (30) calendar days following our dispatch of an e-mail notice to you or thirty (30) calendar days following our posting of notice of the changes on our website. These changes will be effective immediately for new users of the Site. Please note that at all times you are responsible for updating your personal information to provide us with your most current e-mail address. In the event that the last e-mail you have provided us is not valid, or for any reason is not capable of delivering to you the notice described above, our dispatch of the e-mail containing such notice will nonetheless constitute effective notice of the changes described in the notice. In any event, changes to this Privacy Policy may affect our use of Personal Data that you provided us prior to our notification to you of the changes. If you do not wish to permit changes in our use of your personal information, you must notify us prior to the effective date of the changes that you wish to deactivate your account with us. Continued use of the Site following notice of such changes shall indicate your acknowledgement of such changes and agreement to be bound by the terms and conditions of such changes. 

* * *

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the privacy practices of this website, or if you want to exercise any of the rights that you are given under this Privacy Policy, you can contact us using the contact information listed below. 

Gradelink Corporation  
Privacy Officer  
26741 Portola Parkway, Suite 1E-649  
Foothill Ranch, CA 92610  
E-mail: legal@gradelink.com 

© 2014 Gradelink Corp. All rights reserved.  
Terms, conditions, features, availability, pricing, support and service options subject to change without notice.
